<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Recipes on Michael Healy</title>
    <link>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Recipes on Michael Healy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Chipotle Red Potato Salad</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/chipotle-red-potato-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/chipotle-red-potato-salad/</guid>
      <description>Ingredient List    Quantity Ingredient     5 lb Red Potatoes, boiled, cooled, cut into pieces   1 1&amp;frasl;2 cups Whole milk greek yogurt   4 Canned chipotles in adobo sauce, finely diced   2 teaspoons Oregano   2 teaspoons Cumin   2 Limes juiced   1 Red onion sliced thin   1 Green bell pepper, chopped   1 1&amp;frasl;2 Cups Grape or cherry tomatoes, cut in half   To taste Salt and pepper    Instructions  Wisk together lime juice, cumin, oregano, and chipotles in a small bowl.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Barley, Corn, Black Bean, Kale, and Chipotle Salad</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/blackbeansalad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Apr 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/blackbeansalad/</guid>
      <description>I often find myself cooking for myself and the family. One of the largest adjustments over the past year has been my schedule as a graduate student and teaching assistant. This has led to me having odd hours and not being around as often to cook. Out of this I have made a number of recipes that are quick, easy, flavorful, and pack well as leftovers. This is a barley salad that I made to have as a cold option for lunches throughout a school week.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Easy Pork Chops with Mushroom and Marsala Sauce</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/05/easy-pork-chops-with-mushroom-and-marsala-sauce/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 May 2015 17:21:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/05/easy-pork-chops-with-mushroom-and-marsala-sauce/</guid>
      <description>This is a recipe that I took and adapted for a nice, quick, and easy weeknight meal. It could also serve as a good centerpiece for a date or nicer meal as well. It is relatively quick to prepare, though do be sure to not overcook and dry out the pork. Using bone in chops helps with the flavor. In the future I will serve it will rice or noodles to help soak up some of the sauce.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Moroccan Quinoa, Kale, and Chickpea Salad</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/moroccan-quinoa-kale-and-chickpea-salad/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 27 Apr 2015 03:26:50 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/moroccan-quinoa-kale-and-chickpea-salad/</guid>
      <description>It is that time of year again, when the paper deadlines are here, there are papers to grade, and spring birthday parties to attend. To the last point, my friend and fellow blogger had a gathering on Friday. Be sure to check him out at his blog _I&amp;#8217;ll Make a Man Out of You. _It is a lot of fun and he is a fantastic writer.
Anyway, he was having people over for drinks, dinner, and fun times to celebrate his birthday.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Pizzas and Entertaining</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/pizzas-and-entertaining/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Apr 2015 16:16:19 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/pizzas-and-entertaining/</guid>
      <description>Jessi and I made some pizzas for entertaining over the weekend. She made the dough and I took care of many of the topping choices. We made two pizzas, one with sausage, salami, and veggies and the other with bacon, apple, and brie.Bacon, apple, and brie pizza assembly
Both ended up delicious, with good leftovers, and were well enjoyed! We served them with a red and a white wine (I will have to ask what) and they paired well.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Hummus: Garlic and Roasted Red Pepper</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/2015-04-14-hummus-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Apr 2015 17:40:17 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/2015-04-14-hummus-2/</guid>
      <description>This week I decided to make hummus to take to the office to share as a snack and meal accessory. I gathered my supplies and set out to make the two batches: one roasted red pepper and the other garlic.From there it was a quick assembly in my Blendtec Total Blender, blend it, package it, and take it to school with some tortilla chips and some carrots. It&amp;#8217;s been good so far and a great, easy, and healthy snack to bring.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bottling Hot Sauce</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/2015-04-07-bottling-hot-sauce-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Apr 2015 21:22:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/2015-04-07-bottling-hot-sauce-3/</guid>
      <description>I spent some time bottling some delicious homemade hot sauce. These were made from peppers that I had grown last summer and that had been lacto-fermenting in the basement for the past few months. The peppers had been de-stemmed and packed in a ~5% salt brine with other ingredients to ferment. I made two sauces, one red and one green. The green sauce has jalapeño, big jim, mariachi, and arbol peppers along with carrots (not blended), onion, mustard seed, and black peppercorn.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Turkey, Kale, and Pepper Wraps</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/2015-03-13-turkey-kale-and-pepper-wraps/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Mar 2015 16:54:11 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/recipes/2015-03-13-turkey-kale-and-pepper-wraps/</guid>
      <description>One thing that I have found very useful, being a GTA, full-time student, and a stay at home son, is to have lunches pre-prepared and packaged. I can&amp;rsquo;t make sammiches everyday, and making them ahead of time and keeping them in the fridge makes them soggy. I have turned to making wraps on Sunday to take throughout the week that use hearty veggies, some protein, and a whole bunch of delicious.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>