<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Michael Healy</title>
    <link>http://michaelhealy.space/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Michael Healy</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 00:16:23 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://michaelhealy.space/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A New Space and an Update</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/blog/a-new-space-and-an-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 21 May 2017 00:16:23 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/blog/a-new-space-and-an-update/</guid>
      <description>So, there have obviously been some changes here. There are a number of reasons for it, and I will be updating with a longer post eventually. But, there are a number of reasons for the shift, all of which should be good (at least for me, and that&amp;rsquo;s what&amp;rsquo;s important).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Well, I found an Old Post</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/blog/well-i-found-an-old-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2017 03:30:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/blog/well-i-found-an-old-post/</guid>
      <description>I found an old post sitting in drafts, and it made me realize that I have really been meaning to keep up with this whole blog thing, at least somewhat regularly. I mean, it is part of the reason that I have the site, right? It is a good place to keep my various digital projects, and I need to upload a CV, but I want it to be more than just that sort of digital clearinghouse.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Second Semester Go!</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2017/01/second-semester-go/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Jan 2017 04:15:15 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2017/01/second-semester-go/</guid>
      <description>Well we have officially started our second semester at FSU. We had a wonderful time driving home (despite the 48 hours and 2400 miles in the car), and it was really nice to be able to see everyone. We even went to Krug Park 3 times! And ate La Casa 🙂
&amp;nbsp;</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Frameworks and schemas </title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2016/09/frameworks-and-schemas/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 18 Sep 2016 04:06:09 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2016/09/frameworks-and-schemas/</guid>
      <description>&amp;nbsp;Perlman Schema</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>We’re Here!</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2016/09/were-here/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Sep 2016 04:06:13 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2016/09/were-here/</guid>
      <description>Well, we&amp;#8217;ve moved to Tallahassee. In fact, we&amp;#8217;ve been in our apartment a bit over a month now. It&amp;#8217;s been quite the adventure, right pup?Whatever dude.
In that time we&amp;#8217;ve gotten to meet our great cohort, start teaching, find new places, and then this happened:

Well we are all doing alright, although we still have to settle into life here in Florida. It&amp;#8217;s going to be a good adventure, I&amp;#8217;m just not entirely sure what it will all look like yet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Spring Semester and PhD Applications are in</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2016/01/spring-semester-and-phd-applications-are-in/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jan 2016 03:10:30 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2016/01/spring-semester-and-phd-applications-are-in/</guid>
      <description>Long time, no update. It&amp;#8217;s now the second week of the semester, and it feels like there is a lot that has been accomplished and a lot still left to do.
All of the PhD applications are in! So that is a great feeling. I think that I hit submit on the last one around this time last week. So here&amp;#8217;s to playing the waiting game. It feels good to have things out of my control and know that I did everything to make my applications the best possible.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Proceeding</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/12/proceeding/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Dec 2015 00:10:10 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/12/proceeding/</guid>
      <description>Well, this fall semester has been a busy one. I presented at a conference, I&amp;#8217;ve been doing PhD applications, I&amp;#8217;ve been writing a lot, working on a thesis, and teaching two classes. I&amp;#8217;ve been meaning to do more here, perhaps I will soon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Quick Update</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/06/quick-update/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jun 2015 16:54:32 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/06/quick-update/</guid>
      <description>Hey everyone! Sorry about the long delay, the end of the semester and the beginning of the summer have been fun, busy, and adventure filled. I&amp;#8217;ve also had some idea of how this blog will shape and evolve over the next few months as I do intend to keep updating and adapting it.
Here is a preview of some of the thing that I intend to write about: Trip to Colorado, seeing The Mountain Goats, running the 2015 Bolder Boulder, getting back into running, pizza, bacon, running, salads, gardening, peppers, golf, soup, beer, and the general trajectory of life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Why I Run</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/05/why-i-run/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 06 May 2015 21:56:02 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/05/why-i-run/</guid>
      <description>A video essay exploring why I love to run and why I seek out dirt trails to do it. This is 1080p so I advise embiggening it for the best viewing experience.
 </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Three and a Third at Tranquility for a Friday</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/05/three-and-a-third-at-tranquility-for-a-friday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 May 2015 21:59:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/05/three-and-a-third-at-tranquility-for-a-friday/</guid>
      <description>Me Post Halfsy I was excited about being able to get out for a run yesterday. I spent most of last summer and much of the fall running trails with the GOATZ at places like Tranquility, Swanson,Lewis and Clark, Hitchcock, and others. These are all parks in the Greater Omaha Area that have dirt trails that are great for running. Through the GOATZ I&amp;#8217;ve met a bunch of awesome people who pushed me into the best shape of my life.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Only a few emails like this so far</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/only-a-few-emails-like-this-so-far/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Apr 2015 19:21:33 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/only-a-few-emails-like-this-so-far/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Awp 2015</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/awp-2015/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Apr 2015 06:21:49 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/04/awp-2015/</guid>
      <description>So I&amp;#8217;m currently in Minneapolis for the 2015 awp conference and am having a marvelous time. The picture above is of the bookfair on Thursday morning before it got super crazy. That place has been an overwhelming and amazing experience. I&amp;#8217;ve only walked through maybe a third of it so far between sessions. I plan to spend more time there tomorrow.
Today I got to see some very interesting panels on video essays and things that I actually really enjoy writing and doing, so that was good.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Kidding, Life Happened, and I’d Rather Write About That—Part 3</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/just-kidding-life-happened-and-id-rather-write-about-that-part-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Mar 2015 07:09:23 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/just-kidding-life-happened-and-id-rather-write-about-that-part-3/</guid>
      <description>[][1]Grandma is on the left. No date for the picture. My 93-year-old grandmother had a fall and was put into hospice care, as discussed in part 1 and part 2 of this series. We pick it up here after going to visit her one last time.
Mom called at 11:30am on February 15th to let us know that grandma had passed away early that morning. She was comfortable and surrounded by family.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Just Kidding, Life Happened, and I’d Rather Write About That—Part 2</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/just-kidding-life-happened-and-id-rather-write-about-that-part-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Mar 2015 21:18:06 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/just-kidding-life-happened-and-id-rather-write-about-that-part-2/</guid>
      <description>As I explained in my previous post, my grandmother passed away recently and I wanted to explore that. We had left off with me sitting with grandma in hospice.
Mom leaned towards grandma and said, “do you remember your time at University?”
Grandma perked up and looked towards my mother while a little smile turned up the corners of her mouth. My mom motioned for me to grab my iPad with the pictures I had received from the UNO archive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>I Said this was going to be a food blog didn’t I?— Just Kidding, Life happened and my Grandmother Died, I’d rather Write about that—Part 1</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/i-said-this-was-going-to-be-a-food-blog-didnt-i-just-kidding-life-happened-and-my-grandmother-died-id-rather-write-about-that-part-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 16:48:01 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/i-said-this-was-going-to-be-a-food-blog-didnt-i-just-kidding-life-happened-and-my-grandmother-died-id-rather-write-about-that-part-1/</guid>
      <description>I would like to spend some time here exploring the sickness and death of my grandmother and how being a stay-at-home son affected that experience. I hope that by meaningfully reflecting I can share useful insights into dealing with grief. The ultimate purpose of the blog was to give some understanding into being a stay at home son, and to bring some dignity to moving back home. I feel that this can be illuminating into the shifting family dynamics and responsibilities involved in moving home as an adult as well as dealing with the death of a grandparent.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>No Room to Call my Own – Or Why my Bed is in the Family Room</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/no-room-to-call-my-own-or-why-my-bed-is-in-the-family-room/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 06:05:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/no-room-to-call-my-own-or-why-my-bed-is-in-the-family-room/</guid>
      <description>I came home yesterday to find my mother waist deep in my brother’s room attempting to clean out the smell of stale soda, vaping (roasted fruit-loop marshmallow), and dog. She had cleared out some space and was vacuuming an aisle between piles of clothes and computer parts. When I asked what she was doing she responded that the room was gross, reeked of dog, and “anyway, it’s my house.”
My brother had left for the afternoon and my mother had gone to let his dog out when she had reached her breaking point.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meet my Dad and his Magical Made-up Statistics!</title>
      <link>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/five-percent-love-it-the-rest-i-dunno/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Mar 2015 05:24:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://michaelhealy.space/2015/03/five-percent-love-it-the-rest-i-dunno/</guid>
      <description>Last week was my mom’s 57th birthday. My family isn’t big on birthdays except that it is an excuse to go out to eat. Jessi and I met my parents after we got out of class. Dad had a beer and mom already had a glass of wine. We sat down and discussed our days while waiting for my brother to show up. Once he showed up and ordered drinks we settling in for an appetizer of bruschetta (good) and an order of brussel sprouts (holy SHIT amazing!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>